I only bring it up because your ice cream's
melting and it's starting to attract wildlife.
Uh-huh. Do I stay in the jungle
or go towards the beach?
- Doesn't matter, you're looking for treasure.
- Okay.
(Penny:)- Wait, where are you going?
- Go ahead. You're okay.
(Sheldon:)If you run into crocodiles,
just kick them with your boots.
Wanna catch me up?
Well, uh, let's see. She attempted
to open her apartment with her car key...
(Sheldon:)...because her face is overly Midwestern.
Uh...
(Sheldon:)She hasn't had sex in six months.
(Sheldon:)And she ate a fly.
(Penny:)Uh-huh.
(Leonard:)Seriously, six months?
(Penny:)Oh, my God, a treasure chest. I'm rich.
(Sheldon:)Level three and she thinks she's rich.
What a newb.
(Raj:)Okay, we're all set.